https://coachsuewest.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Coach Sue West
HomeBlogCoaching ServicesAdults with ADHD (or similar symptoms)Self-Employed/Work at HomeIn TransitionAbout SueProgramsSpeaking/ProgramsMy Organizing BookADHD Workbook Privacy Policy Usage Terms and ConditionsThe content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information mentioned on this website meet your specific requirements.This website contains material which is owned by us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited by any means, digital or otherwise, is expressly prohibited.Links to Other WebsitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Privacy of Personal InformationWe are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should you provide information when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.If you have subscribed to our blog and/or newsletter mailing list, you may unsubscribe at any time by using the Unsubscribe form in the sidebar of the website or contacting us directly.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.TweetPinShare0 SharesAt this time I am not taking on new clients and so have these two recommendations for you. Both are people I have known for years and trust. Both are experienced and well rounded with different skill sets; read more about them on their About Us pages.For coaching services/ADHD expertise: Helen Montfort, PCC, COC®, Making Space for LifeFor virtual organizing U.S. or in person organizing in the NH/MA areas: Kim Cox, PackRat Solutions Level I Certificate of Study in Chronic Disorganization, Institute for Challenging Disorganization® (ICD); Level I Certificate of Study in Understanding Hoarding Behavior, Institute for Challenging Disorganization® (ICD)
Testimonials
"These meetings with Sue have brought me clarity, have helped me set and accomplish business and personal goals, satisfaction of completion, but most of all “Time” to do some of things I enjoy doing. She has helped me stop the juggling act.""Sue’s book leaves no stone unturned, no question unanswered … Whether it’s stuff, time, perspective or plans, she presents clear, easy-to-follow suggestions and ideas that help the reader clarify what’s important and how to let go of the rest. … from a holistic standpoint, taking into account the emotional and relational factors that are so often at the core of our difficulties…."Her work is based on the recognition that our lives are a series of stages or chapters, and that each new stage has its own requirements for a successful and fulfilling transition. It can often feel like an overwhelming challenge to manage such transitions deliberately and mindfully. Sue’s robust and encouraging approach to this challenge makes it possible to break down and eliminate even the most daunting-looking obstacles." Kathryn May, MSW, Life Coach and Therapist"Our conversations made all the difference in my getting both an emotional and organizational grasp on the road map for sorting and moving.
Again, just having you to talk through the process with me made the difference I needed to focus and design a doable plan of attack. … my reframing the move to one of “going ahead” rather than “leaving behind” was the shift for emotional motivation I needed. Honestly, I’d still be stuck without having asked for help and reached out to you. The concept of roadmaps – and the other pearl of using the ladies room for a quiet place before speaking etc… will stick with me forever as GREAT tools!"“Sue West brings a librarian style sensibility to organizing while offering advice that is easily accessible to everyone….the art of reorganizing to suit your values and to help you through life transitions…. She emphasizes that there is no right or wrong way to organize. ….aims to overcome any fear individuals have about getting organized by encouraging small steps….She discusses organizing as an “ongoing process” and encourages communication among those who share living space to avoid unintentionally sabotaging any strides toward a more ordered household. … As an archives consultant who helps families create order for their personal papers, and as a former professional librarian, I recommend this book to anyone who bemoans lacking an innate sense of how to order their world.It is also helpful for those who need a new perspective to help rethink their possessions and to re-examine their sense of self to step comfortably into the future. Ms. West’s book will walk you through the steps you need to create an organizational system that works for you and makes you feel in control."Melissa Mannon, Archives and Cultural Heritage Consultant, ArchivesInfo“Instructor was compassionate, knowledgeable and encouraged participants to actively speak up and express themselves.
Extremely helpful in planning future goals.”"Working with Sue West is working with someone who is “all in!” Fully focused, engaged
and insightful is how I would describe our interactions. Sue is skillful in listening and providing the feedback that makes me want to take action! Getting unstuck is what I needed and I am very grateful for Sue’s expertise in removing the glue from my shoes!"What clients are sayingReviews for Organize for a Fresh StartPractical Strategies in Your InboxSubscribe to read practical strategies to common challenges, either as they're published or as a monthly summary.Read a sample | Sign up here!Blog CategoriesAD/HDBest of Blogs-Start HereBook Reviews for My BooksBusiness Organizing/Home OfficeChangeCommunicationsDecision MakingDownsize, RightsizeFinancesHolidaysHome OrganizationInterviews and Guest PostsLife "Balance"Papers and/or TechnologyProductivity OR ADHD Tips – Videos – 2 minutes eachSelf CareTime ManagementWorking on ProjectsADHD Self-Paced Workbook Save Printed workbook  Kindle version Coach Sue West Copyright © 2020 Website by Janet Barclay Privacy Policy
603 765-9267Sue@CoachSueWest.com
